Thank you. What can I bring for you on
this glorious afternoon? Well Hector here's the game plan, you know
bring us to Absolute Point teenies. You know how
I like em straight up and then precisely 7 and 1/2
minutes after that. You're going to bring us two
more then two more after that every five minutes until one
of us passes the fuck out let strategy sir.
I'm good with water for now though. Thank you.
His first day on Wall Street give him time.
Thank you. Mmm. Thank you.
Mr. You were able to do drugs during the
day and still function still do your job fuck else. Would
you do this job cocaine and hookers my friend,
right?
I gotta say I'm incredibly excited to be a
part of a firm. I mean the clients you have or
absolutely talk to clients. Your only responsibility is to
put meat on the table.
You got a girlfriend. I'm married. I have no
wife or name's Teresa to Cuts here. Congratulations. Thank you. Think
about Teresa name of the game move the money
from your clients pocket into your pocket. Right? But if you
can make a clients money at the same time,
it's advantageous. Everyone them. Correct? No.
number one rule of Wall Street
Nobody I don't care if you're Warren Buffett, or
if you Jimmy Buffett, nobody knows if the stock is going
to go up down sideways or in fucking circles
at least of all stockbrokers is all the fugazi in order
for guys is fugazi. It's a fake if you
forgot see it's a wise idea to lose your tooth fairy
dust. It doesn't exist. It's never landed. It is
no matter it's not on the elemental chart it it's not
fucking real Stay With Me.
We don't create shit. We don't build anything. No,
so if you got a client who bought stock at 8
and it now sits at 16 and he's all
fucking happy. He wants to cash in liquidate take his fucking
money at run home. You don't let him do
that because that would make it real, right? No. What do
you do you get another brilliant idea especially idea
another situation another stock to reinvest his earnings and then te
and he will every single time because they're fucking
addicted.
You just keep doing this again and again and
again meanwhile.
He thinks he's getting shit Rich, which he is
on paper. But you and me the Brokers. We're taking home
Cold Hard Cash via commission motherfucker, right?
That's incredible serum. Can't tell you how excited I
am. You should be it's two keys to success in the
broker business. First of all.
You gotta stay relaxed. Yeah, you jerk-off.
But do I jerk off? Yeah. Yeah jerk off
here. Let me times a week.
Like 3/4 3/4 times me pump those numbers out.
There's a rookie numbers in this racket. I myself I jerk
off at least twice a day. Wow, once in
the morning right after a workout and then once right after
lunch, really, okay, I want to that's not why
I do it I do it because I fucking need to
think about your dealing with numbers all day long
decimal points high frequencies Nang bang bang fucking digits ticket or
very acidic above the shoulders mustard shit can tweak
some people out right? You got to feed the geese to
keep the blood flowing. I keep the Rhythm below
the belt done. This is not a tip. This is a
prescription. Trust me. If you don't you will fall
out of balance split your differential and tip the fuck over
or worse yet.
I've seen this happen implode. I don't want to
implode certain know you don't I'm in it for the long
run, you know. Yeah implosions are ugly. Yeah, pop
off to the bathroom work one at any time you can
and when you get really good at it, you'll
fucking be stroking it. You'll be thinking about money.
Second key to success in this racket. Is this
little baby right here? It's called cocaine, right? It will keep
you sharp between the ears. They'll also help your
fingers dial faster. And guess what? That's good for me. Yes,
sir.
Revolutions you follow revolutions keep the clients on the
ferris wheel and I goes the Park is open 24/7 365
every decade every goddamn Century. That's it name of
the game.
How can a key? Hmm? Thank you.
mmm
Come with a common denominator.
see ya out of Mana comes in prayed comes
down going down Broadway is a one way street whichever way
I